Register of the Leopold Labedz papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1926-1992
  - Kotze, D. J., 1981 (Box-folder 19: 58)
  - Koumjian, Vaughn, 1968 (Box-folder 19: 59)
  - Kovanic, Edward F., 1971 (Box-folder 19: 60)
  - Kowczyk, A. C., 1975 (Box-folder 19: 61)
  - Kraft, Mary Ellen, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 19: 62)
  - Kramer, John M., 1985 (Box-folder 19: 63)
  - Krasnow, Wladislaw, 1975 (Box-folder 19: 64)
  - Kraus, T. Peter, 1969 (Box-folder 19: 65)
  - Krejci, Jaroslav, 1974 (Box-folder 19: 66)
  - Kristol, Irving, 1957-1977 (Box-folder 19: 67)
  - Krygier, H. Richard, 1960-1985 (Box-folder 19: 68)
  - Krzywicki, Jerzy, 1962 (Box-folder 19: 69)
  - Kuhlman, J. A., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Kulczycki, J., 1986 (Box-folder 20: 2)
  - Kultura, circa 1950 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Kurman, Suzanne, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Kuznetsov, Anatoly, 1975 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Kwak, Chung Hwan, undated (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Kyle, Keith to Litvinov, Pavel, 1974, 1977 (Box-folder 20: 7)
  - K - general, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - La Pira, Giorgio, 1961 (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - Laba, Roman, 1986 (Box-folder 20: 10)
  - Labedz, Jakub, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 20: 11)
  - Labedz, Leopold, 1957-1982 (Box-folder 20: 12)
    Comprised of template letters written by Labedz. Difficult to decipher intended recipient.
  - Labedz, Marek, 1960 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Labedz, Natalie, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Labedz, Yvette, 1950-1963 (Box-folder 20: 15)
  - Laber, Jeri, undated (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Laird, Robbin, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 20: 17)
  - Lake, Michael, 1969 (Box-folder 20: 18)
  - Lambert, J. W., 1968 (Box-folder 20: 19)
  - Lange, Fred G., 1971 (Box-folder 20: 20)
  - Langslet, Lars Roar, 1962 (Box-folder 20: 21)
  - Laqueur, Walter, 1960-1979 (Box-folder 20: 22)
  - Larrabee, Stephen F., 1972, 1976 (Box-folder 20: 23)
  - Larry, Richard M., 1977 (Box-folder 20: 24)
  - Larsen, Axel, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 20: 25)
  - Lasky, Floria, 1971, 1973 (Box-folder 20: 26)
  - Lasky, Melvin J., 1963-1986 (Box-folder 20: 27)
  - Lasota, Irena, 1986 (Box-folder 20: 28)
  - Late Night Line-Up, BBC, 1968 (Box-folder 20: 29)
  - Laurens, Valeria, 1970 (Box-folder 20: 30)
  - Lawrence, John, 1976 (Box-folder 20: 31)
  - Lawson, Nigel, 1970 (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - Laychuk, J. L., 1976 (Box-folder 21: 2)
  - Layton, Ann M., 1971 (Box-folder 21: 3)
  - Lazitch, Branko, 1974 (Box-folder 21: 4)
  - Lebahan, Axel, 1978 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - Ledeen, Michael, 1979 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Lederer, Ivo J., 1966-1978 (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Lee, Eric, 1986 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Lefever, Ernest W., 1978 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Leggett, G. H., 1979 (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Lehmann, Rosamond, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Lehrman, Edgar H., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Leibman, Morris I., 1977-1979 (Box-folder 21: 13)
  - Leifer, Michael, 1986 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Leigh, Michael, 1974 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Leighton, Marian, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Lekachman, Robert, undated (Box-folder 21: 17)
  - Lendvai, Paule, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 21: 18)
  - Lenkowsky, Leslie, 1979 (Box-folder 21: 19)
  - Lenski, Branko, 1976 (Box-folder 21: 20)
  - Lenz, Siegfried, 1973 (Box-folder 21: 21)
  - Lepage, Henri, 1980 (Box-folder 21: 22)
  - Leprince-Ringuet, Louis, 1973 (Box-folder 21: 23)
  - Lerner, Michael, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 21: 24)
  - Lerski, 1973 (Box-folder 21: 25)
  - Letters concerning unpublished articles, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 21: 26)
  - Letters to the Headmistress, 1969 (Box-folder 21: 27)
    Comprised of correspondence regarding school admission of Labedz's daughter, Natalia.
  - Letter to the Times, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 21: 28)
  - Letter to the Times, Czechoslovakia, 1968 (Box-folder 21: 29)
  - Letter to the Times, Polish professors, 1968 (Box-folder 21: 30)
  - Lévesque, Jacques, 1972 (Box-folder 21: 31)
  - Levi, Arrigo, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 21: 32)
  - Levin, Bernard, 1967-1978 (Box-folder 21: 33)
  - Levin, C., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 21: 34)
  - Levitas, S. M., 1959 (Box-folder 21: 35)
  - Levy, Margo, undated (Box-folder 21: 36)
  - Lewin, M., Dr., 1975 (Box-folder 21: 37)
  - Lewis, Bernard, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 21: 38)
  - Lewis, John Wilson, 1973 (Box-folder 21: 39)
  - Lichtheim, George, 1957-1958, 1973 (Box-folder 21: 40)
  - Liebert, Georges, 1974, 1978 (Box-folder 21: 41)
  - Liehm, D., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21: 42)
  - Lieven, Alexander, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 21: 43)
  - Lifshitz, Danielle, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Lindblad, J. Thomas, 1971 (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Lindblom, Charles E., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - Linderski, J., 1979 (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - Lindley, Frances, Mrs., 1971 (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Lindmajer, Maria, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Linton, R. A., Major, 1971 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Linz, Juan J., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Lionel Bloch and Co., 1970, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Lippman, Harley, 1977 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Lipset, Seymour M., 1969-1977 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Lisann, Maury, 1969 (Box-folder 22: 12)
  - Lisicky, Vera, 1976 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Lisiecka, Alicja, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Literature and Revolution, correspondence with contributors, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Little, Richard, Dr., 1968 (Box-folder 22: 16)
  - Litvinoff, Emanuel, 1974 (Box-folder 22: 17)
  - Litwak, Robert S., 1985 (Box-folder 22: 18)
  - Litwin, Aleksander, 1972 (Box-folder 22: 19)
  - Llewellyn, Algernon, 1972 (Box-folder 22: 20)
  - Lloyd-Jones, Antonia, 1985 (Box-folder 22: 21)
  - Lobos, S., 1961 (Box-folder 22: 22)
  - Logan, Fred J., 1974 (Box-folder 22: 23)
  - de Loisy, Solange, 1971 (Box-folder 22: 24)
  - Lolo, undated (Box-folder 22: 25)
  - London, Kurt L., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 22: 26)
  - Lopez-Morillas, Juan, 1973 (Box-folder 22: 27)
  - Loss, Richard, 1972 (Box-folder 22: 28)
  - Lottich, Kenneth V., 1962 (Box-folder 22: 29)
  - Louis, Victor, 1969 (Box-folder 22: 30)
  - Lowe, Ernst, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 22: 31)
  - Lowe, J. C., 1961 (Box-folder 22: 32)
  - Lowe, Peter, 1984 (Box-folder 22: 33)
  - Lowenthal, Richard, 1960-1981 (Box-folder 22: 34)
  - Luck, David, 1970 (Box-folder 22: 35)
  - Lunghi, Hugh, 1992 (Box-folder 22: 36)
  - Luryi, Yuri, 1978 (Box-folder 22: 37)
  - Luttwak, Edward N., 1978 (Box-folder 22: 38)
  - Lwoff, Andre, 1973 (Box-folder 22: 39)
  - Lydolph, Paul E., 1969 (Box-folder 22: 40)
  - Lyman, Richard, 1971, 1981 (Box-folder 22: 41)
  - Lynch, Kevin, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 42)
  - L - general, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 22: 43)
  - MacDougall, H., 1970 (Box-folder 22: 44)
  - Mace, Edward, 1968 (Box-folder 22: 45)
  - MacFarquhar, Roderick, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 22: 46)
  - Machovec, Charles, undated (Box-folder 22: 47)
  - MacInnes, Colin, 1959, 1967 (Box-folder 22: 48)
  - MacIntyre, Alasdair, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 22: 49)
  - Mack, Charles L., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 22: 50)
  - MacKinnon, Sally K., 1961 (Box-folder 22: 51)
  - MacLehose, Christopher, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 22: 52)
  - Macleod, Alex, 1979 (Box-folder 22: 53)
  - Macoveanu, Petre, 1968 (Box-folder 22: 54)
  - Macrae, Donald G., 1967 (Box-folder 22: 55)
  - MacRae, Susan, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 22: 56)
  - Maggie, 1974 (Box-folder 22: 57)
  - Magocsi, Paul R., 1974 (Box-folder 22: 58)
  - Maichel, K., 1968 (Box-folder 22: 59)
  - Mairet, Philip, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 22: 60)
  - Majendie, A. E., 1972 (Box-folder 22: 61)
  - Maksimov, Vladimir, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 22: 62)
  - Malcolm, 1986 (Box-folder 22: 63)
  - Malia, Martin, 1973 (Box-folder 22: 64)
  - Malvehy, Graciela, 1968 (Box-folder 22: 65)
  - Mancall, Mark, 1962-1981 (Box-folder 22: 66)
  - Manning, Robert, 1960 (Box-folder 22: 67)
  - Manry, A. G., 1970 (Box-folder 22: 68)
  - Mantle, W. P., 1973, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 69)
  - Maravel, Joanna, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 22: 70)
  - Marcus, Alfred, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 22: 71)
  - Marcus, Philip N., 1982 (Box-folder 22: 72)
  - Maria, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 22: 73)
  - Marian, undated (Box-folder 22: 74)
  - Marion, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 22: 75)
  - Markham, Gervase, 1969 (Box-folder 22: 76)
  - Marks, Neil Alan, 1969 (Box-folder 22: 77)
  - Marquand, David, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Marsh, Caryl, 1972 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Marshall, 1963 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - Marshall, Richard H., 1969 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Martin, Andrea, 1977 (Box-folder 23: 5)
  - Martin, David J., 1977 (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - Martin, Edward, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Masani, Minoo R., 1975-1989 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Maslakovic, Srdana, 1986 (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - Mason, Caroline, 1980 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Masters, Derek, Esq., 1968 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Masterson, Aileen, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Mastny, Vojtech, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Matthews, Lilidmilez, 1976 (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - de Mauny, Erik, 1969 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Maureen, 1962 (Box-folder 23: 16)
  - Mauriac, François, 1966 (Box-folder 23: 17)
  - Maurice, 1976 (Box-folder 23: 18)
  - Max, 1962 (Box-folder 23: 19)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1977 (Box-folder 23: 20)
  - Mazières, M., 1969 (Box-folder 23: 21)
  - Mazrui, Ali A., 1971-1976 (Box-folder 23: 22)
  - McCabe, Edward, undated (Box-folder 23: 23)
  - McCaffrey, Neil, 1977 (Box-folder 23: 24)
  - McCallum, D., 1960 (Box-folder 23: 25)
  - McCarroll, Michael, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 23: 26)
  - McDonald, John W., Jr., 1972, 1976 (Box-folder 23: 27)
  - McDowell, Edwin, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 28)
  - McGurn, William J., 1984-1985 (Box-folder 23: 29)
  - McIlhenny, Helen, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 23: 30)
  - McInnes, Neil, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 23: 31)
  - McKenna, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 32)
  - McLinn, William, 1970 (Box-folder 23: 33)
  - McMenamin, Edward B., 1962 (Box-folder 23: 34)
  - McMichael, 1977 (Box-folder 23: 35)
  - McMillan, Priscilla Johnson, 1969 (Box-folder 23: 36)
  - McNeal, Robert H., 1977 (Box-folder 23: 37)
  - Meana, Carlo Ripa de, 1977 (Box-folder 23: 38)
  - Medek, Ivan, 1982 (Box-folder 23: 39)
  - Medlin, Virgil Dewain, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 23: 40)
  - Medvedev, Z. A., 1975 (Box-folder 23: 41)
  - Meeûs, Anthony de, 1967 (Box-folder 23: 42)
  - Megrian, Leon D., 1973 (Box-folder 23: 43)
  - Mehnert, Klaus, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 44)
  - Mehta, Asoka, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 45)
  - Merriam, Kendall A., 1981 (Box-folder 23: 46)
  - Merton, Alan, 1970 (Box-folder 23: 47)
  - Merton, Robert K., 1958 (Box-folder 23: 48)
  - Meteyer, Beatrice L., 1971 (Box-folder 23: 49)
  - Metz, Eugene L., 1962 (Box-folder 23: 50)
  - Meyer, Alfred G., 1970 (Box-folder 23: 51)
  - Mezz, Jon, 1971 (Box-folder 23: 52)
  - Mgarasino, Alberto, 1985 (Box-folder 23: 53)
  - Mianowicz, Tomasz, undated (Box-folder 23: 54)
  - Michael, 1960 (Box-folder 23: 55)
  - Michael, Franz, 1963 (Box-folder 23: 56)
  - Michael, J., 1969 (Box-folder 23: 57)
  - Michaeli, Daniel, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 23: 58)
  - Michaelis, Diana, 1976 (Box-folder 23: 59)
  - Michaels, Carol, 1977 (Box-folder 23: 60)
  - Michel, 1966 (Box-folder 23: 61)
  - Mieli, Renato, 1968, 1975 (Box-folder 23: 62)
  - Mieroszewski, J., undated (Box-folder 23: 63)
  - Mihailovich, Vasa D., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 23: 64)
  - Mihajlov, Mihajlo, 1985 (Box-folder 23: 65)
  - Mike, 1963-1976 (Box-folder 23: 66)
  - Milchsack, Lilo, 1964 (Box-folder 23: 67)
  - Miles, Barrington T., 1968 (Box-folder 23: 68)
  - Miller, J. D. B., 1963 (Box-folder 23: 69)
  - Miller, Jack, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 23: 70)
  - Miller, William J., 1968 (Box-folder 23: 71)
  - Milner, Diana, 1967 (Box-folder 23: 72)
  - Milnikiel, E. J., 1957 (Box-folder 23: 73)
  - Miłosz, Czesław, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 74)
  - Mindlin, Murray, Mr. and Mrs., 1959-1980 (Box-folder 23: 75)
  - Minellin, Masha, 1961 (Box-folder 23: 76)
  - Minogue, Ken, 1956-1984 (Box-folder 23: 77)
  - Miskiewicz, Sophia M., 1985 (Box-folder 23: 78)
  - Misztal, Bronisław, 1981 (Box-folder 23: 79)
  - Miyazaki, Joe, 1960 (Box-folder 23: 80)
  - Moatti, Gérard, 1970 (Box-folder 23: 81)
  - von Mohrenschildt, D., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 23: 82)
  - Monahan, J. E., 1966 (Box-folder 23: 83)
  - Monegal, Emir Rodriguez, 1967 (Box-folder 23: 84)
  - Monteiro, J. B., 1970 (Box-folder 23: 85)
  - Montias, John Michael, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Moore, Belinda, undated (Box-folder 24: 2)
  - Moore, Daniel, 1978 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Moore, Richard, 1962 (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - Morgan, Patrick, 1970 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Morin, Edgar, 1973 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Morris, 1962 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Morris, Arthur R., 1970 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Morris, Bernard S., 1972-1974 (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Morris, J. J., 1962 (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Morse, John H., 1974-1976 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Morton, undated (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - Mosely, Philip E., 1963 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Mount, Ferdinand, 1979 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Mowbray, Rose, 1961 (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 24: 16)
  - Mphahlele, Ezekiel, 1962 (Box-folder 24: 17)
  - Mrożek, Sławomir, 1968 (Box-folder 24: 18)
  - Mueller, M. G., 1970 (Box-folder 24: 19)
  - Muggeridge, Malcolm, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 24: 20)
  - Munell, Kathy, 1969 (Box-folder 24: 21)
  - Munro, Dale P., 1969 (Box-folder 24: 22)
  - Munson, Steven C., 1976 (Box-folder 24: 23)
  - Murphy, Ken, 1976 (Box-folder 24: 24)
  - Murphy, Patrick M., 1973 (Box-folder 24: 25)
  - Murray, 1971 (Box-folder 24: 26)
  - Musgrove, A. K., 1969 (Box-folder 24: 27)
  - Musti, Bruno, 1972 (Box-folder 24: 28)
  - M - general, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 24: 29)
  - Nabokov, Nicolas, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 24: 30)
  - Nadeau, Maurice, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24: 31)
  - Nagorski, Zygmunt, 1970 (Box-folder 24: 32)
  - Najder, Zdzisław, 1985 (Box-folder 24: 33)
  - Nakai, Yoshinori, 1974 (Box-folder 24: 34)
  - Le Nan, Maurice, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 24: 35)
  - Naoi, Takeo, 1974 (Box-folder 24: 36)
  - Narayan, Jayprakash, 1959 (Box-folder 24: 37)
  - Nathan, James A., 1976 (Box-folder 24: 38)
  - Navrozov, Lev, 1979 (Box-folder 24: 39)
  - Naylor, Diana, 1986 (Box-folder 24: 40)
  - Nekrasov, Victor, 1977 (Box-folder 24: 41)
  - Nekrich, A. M., 1976-1978 (Box-folder 24: 42)
  - Nelson, Brian, 1970 (Box-folder 24: 43)
  - Nelson, Daniel N., 1975 (Box-folder 24: 44)
  - Nemoianu, Virgil, 1978 (Box-folder 24: 45)
  - Nenning, Gunther, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 24: 46)
  - Neogy, Rajat, 1970 (Box-folder 24: 47)
  - The New Statesman, 1975 (Box-folder 24: 48)
  - Ng-Quinn, Michael, 1982 (Box-folder 24: 49)
  - Nicholls, John, Dr., 1975 (Box-folder 24: 50)
  - Nicholson, Michael, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 24: 51)
  - Nickel, Herman, 1977 (Box-folder 24: 52)
  - de Nicolay, France, 1985 (Box-folder 24: 53)
  - Nielsen, Waldemar A., 1979 (Box-folder 24: 54)
  - Nisbet, Robert, 1979 (Box-folder 24: 55)
  - Nish, Dan, 1979 (Box-folder 24: 56)
  - Nitze, Paul, 1978 (Box-folder 24: 57)
  - Nocall, Ksenia A., 1978 (Box-folder 24: 58)
  - Noeller, Paul E., 1972 (Box-folder 24: 59)
  - North, Robert C., 1961 (Box-folder 24: 60)
  - Nove, Alec, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 24: 61)
  - Nowak, Jadwiga, 1976 (Box-folder 24: 62)
  - Nowak, Jan, 1966-1979 (Box-folder 24: 63)
  - Nowakowski, Tadeusz, 1960 (Box-folder 24: 64)
  - Nunez, Julio A., 1985 (Box-folder 24: 65)
  - Nutsch, James G., 1971 (Box-folder 24: 66)
  - Nyary, Nicholas, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 24: 67)
  - Nye, J. S., 1967 (Box-folder 24: 68)
  - Nyman, I., 1977 (Box-folder 24: 69)
  - Oakes, John B., 1973 (Box-folder 24: 70)
  - O'Brien, Patrick, 1972 (Box-folder 24: 71)
  - The Observer, 1974 (Box-folder 24: 72)
  - Odom, William, 1975, 1979 (Box-folder 24: 73)
  - OECD (Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development) Information Service, 1971 (Box-folder 24: 74)
  - Ojilas, Milovan, 1970 (Box-folder 24: 75)
  - O'Keeffe, Denis, 1985 (Box-folder 24: 76)
  - Ola (Aleksandra), undated (Box-folder 24: 77)
  - Oliver, Magdalena, 1970 (Box-folder 24: 78)
  - Olver, A. S. B., 1958 (Box-folder 24: 79)
  - Olvey, Lee D., 1972 (Box-folder 24: 80)
  - van Oort, H. A., Dr., 1973 (Box-folder 24: 81)
  - ORBIS, 1971 (Box-folder 24: 82)
  - Oren, Nissan, 1968 (Box-folder 24: 83)
  - Osborn, Edward, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 24: 84)
  - Osborne, Felicity, 1974 (Box-folder 24: 85)
  - Osers, Ewald, 1970 (Box-folder 24: 86)
  - Oshima, Yasumasa, 1968 (Box-folder 24: 87)
  - Ossowski, Stanisław, 1956 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Ostro, Ernest A., 1970 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Ostrowski, J., 1969 (Box-folder 25: 3)
  - Ota, Hirokazu, 1985 (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - Owaki, Jun-ichiro, 1977 (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - Owen, Peter, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Oxford University Press, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - O - general, undated (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Padhye, Prabhakar, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 25: 9)
  - Paeschke, Hans, 1967 (Box-folder 25: 10)
  - Painter, B. G., 1969-1974 (Box-folder 25: 11)
  - Pais, A., 1979 (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - Paloczi-Horvath, George, 1960 (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - Paluchowski, Andrzej, 1986 (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - Pampuch, Wanda, 1959 (Box-folder 25: 15)
  - van Panhuys, Christian, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Panin, Dimitri, undated (Box-folder 25: 17)
  - Papaioannou, Kostas, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 25: 18)
  - Paret, Peter, 1971 (Box-folder 25: 19)
  - Paris, 1962 February - 1964 January (Box-folder 25: 20-22)
  - Parkinson, Anna, 1985 (Box-folder 25: 23)
  - Parks, Mina E., 1969 (Box-folder 25: 24)
  - Parrett, R. C., 1961 (Box-folder 25: 25)
  - Paternostro, S., undated (Box-folder 25: 26)
  - Paterson, I. D., 1978 (Box-folder 25: 27)
  - Patron, J. F., 1973 (Box-folder 25: 28)
  - Patterson, Sheila, 1982 (Box-folder 25: 29)
  - Paukert, Liba, 1985 (Box-folder 25: 30)
  - Paul, Routledge and Kegan, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 25: 31)
  - Pavlowitch, Stevan, 1970 (Box-folder 25: 32)
  - Pax Christi International, 1978 (Box-folder 25: 33)
  - Payne, Samuel Burton, Jr., 1973 (Box-folder 25: 34)
  - Peckham, Morse, 1973 (Box-folder 25: 35)
  - Peldzus, Ute, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 25: 36)
  - Pendill, C. Grant, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 25: 37)
  - Penguin Books, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 25: 38)
  - Pennar, Jaan, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 25: 39)
  - Pennycook, Andrew, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 40)
  - Penrose, Rebecca, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 25: 41)
  - Peretz, Martin, 1976 (Box-folder 25: 42)
  - Perkins, Larry, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 25: 43)
  - Perle, Richard, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 25: 44)
  - Pervan, Ralph, 1973 (Box-folder 25: 45)
  - Perznowski, Lucjan, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 46)
  - Peterborough, 1968 (Box-folder 25: 47)
  - Peters, Ann, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 25: 48)
  - Peters, Lana (Svetlana Iosifovna Alliluyeva), 1979 (Box-folder 25: 49)
  - Peterson, William, 1970 (Box-folder 25: 50)
  - Pethybridge, Roger, undated (Box-folder 25: 51)
  - Petrov, Vladimir, 1968 (Box-folder 25: 52)
  - Philippovich, T., 1960-1961 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Philips, Claude S., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Phillips, William, 1961 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Pick, Hella, 1978 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Pick, O., 1982 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Piddubcheshen, Eva, 1962 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Pieire, undated (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - Pillar, William, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Pillsbury, George S., 1976 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Pilon, 1982 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Pinder, John, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Pini, Massimo, 1977 (Box-folder 26: 12)
  - Pio, 1963 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - Piper, Leonard, 1973 (Box-folder 26: 14)
  - Pipes, Richard, 1959-1985 (Box-folder 26: 15)
  - Pistor, Michael, 1977 (Box-folder 26: 16)
  - Plant, Marjorie, 1963 (Box-folder 26: 17)
  - Plastrik, Stanley, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 26: 18)
  - Platt, F., 1971 (Box-folder 26: 19)
  - Platt, Jennifer, 1971 (Box-folder 26: 20)
  - Plimley, Wendy A., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 26: 21)
  - Ploss, Sidney, 1970 (Box-folder 26: 22)
  - Podgirecki, Adam, 1972 (Box-folder 26: 23)
  - Podgórski, 1975 (Box-folder 26: 24)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 26: 25)
  - Pohribny, Arsen, 1969 (Box-folder 26: 26)
  - Pol, Galai, 1974 (Box-folder 26: 27)
  - Polanyi, Michael, 1960 (Box-folder 26: 28)
  - Pollak, Paul, 1970 (Box-folder 26: 29)
  - Pollard, Sidney, 1971 (Box-folder 26: 30)
  - Polska Szkoła Przedmiotów Ojczystych, 1969 (Box-folder 26: 31)
  - Pomian, John, 1979 (Box-folder 26: 32)
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 26: 33)
  - Popovsky, Mark, 1978 (Box-folder 26: 34)
  - Popper, Karl, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 26: 35)
  - Porsolt, Josef, 1969 (Box-folder 26: 36)
  - Porter, Diana, 1969 (Box-folder 26: 37)
  - Pospielovsky, D., 1963-1979 (Box-folder 26: 38)
  - Pospieszalski, A., 1978 (Box-folder 26: 39)
  - Possev-Verlog, 1969 (Box-folder 26: 40)
  - Postan, Michael, 1960, 1968 (Box-folder 26: 41)
  - Powell, David, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 26: 42)
  - Powers, David, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 26: 43)
  - Powling, Susan, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 26: 44)
  - Praeger, Frederick, 1960-1989 (Box-folder 26: 45)
  - Preiss, Al, 1966 (Box-folder 26: 46)
  - Prendergast, Curtis, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 26: 47)
  - Preston, Peter, 1968 (Box-folder 26: 48)
  - Price, James, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 26: 49)
  - Printers (107), 1979-1981 (Box-folder 26: 50)
    Correspondence with the printers office regarding offprints for Survey issue 107.
  - Priscilla, 1968 (Box-folder 26: 51)
  - Prital, David, 1974 (Box-folder 26: 52)
  - Pritchard, G. J., 1969 (Box-folder 26: 53)
  - Prokopowicz, T., 1970 (Box-folder 26: 54)
  - Prybyla, Jan S., 1977 (Box-folder 26: 55)
  - Psomiades, Harry, 1970 (Box-folder 26: 56)
  - P - general, 1959, 1970, 1980 (Box-folder 26: 57)
  - Quest, undated (Box-folder 26: 58)
  - Ra'anan, Gavriel, undated (Box-folder 26: 59)
  - Ra'anan, Uri, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 26: 60)
  - Rabkin, Yakov, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 26: 61)
  - Racadio, Bernadette, 1972 (Box-folder 26: 62)
  - Raczynski, Edward, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 63)
  - Rahman, Hossainur, undated (Box-folder 26: 64)
  - Rahr, Gleb, 1967 (Box-folder 26: 65)
  - Rahr, Lev A., 1966-1975 (Box-folder 26: 66)
  - Raina, Peter, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 26: 67)
  - Ramet, Pedro, 1985 (Box-folder 26: 68)
  - Ramoth, Thomas, 1967 (Box-folder 26: 69)
  - Randolph, Rosemary, 1974 (Box-folder 26: 70)
  - Rapp, Helen, 1968 (Box-folder 26: 71)
  - Rapp, Uri, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Raqozin, Marion, 1962 (Box-folder 27: 2)
  - Raule, Ann, 1962 (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - Raun, Toivo U., 1973 (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - Ray, Marie Louise, 1962 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Ray, Sibnarayan, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Rebecca, 1985 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Recht, Anne-Liese, 1962 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Reddaway, Peter, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Rees, Jenny, 1986 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Regan, Diane, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Reidel Publishing Co., 1969 (Box-folder 27: 12)
  - Reiff, Diner and Co., 1974 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Remington, Robin A., 1970 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - Renoux, Jacques, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 15)
  - Reve, Karl von Het, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Revel, Jean-François, 1970, 1982 (Box-folder 27: 17)
  - Reyman, Carl, 1961 (Box-folder 27: 18)
  - Rezler, Julius, 1973 (Box-folder 27: 19)
  - Rhode, Gotthold, undated (Box-folder 27: 20)
  - Rhodes, Kent, 1976 (Box-folder 27: 21)
  - Richards, Susan, 1978 (Box-folder 27: 22)
  - Richardson, Randolph R., 1977-1982 (Box-folder 27: 23)
  - Richert, Ernst, 1966 (Box-folder 27: 24)
  - von Riekhoff, Harald, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 27: 25)
  - Rigby, T. H., 1976 (Box-folder 27: 26)
  - Rios, René Alvarez, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 27)
  - Riouhel, Giorgio, undated (Box-folder 27: 28)
  - Ritter, Gerhard A., 1970 (Box-folder 27: 29)
  - Riveles, Stanley, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 27: 30)
  - Roberti, Vero, 1967 (Box-folder 27: 31)
  - Roberts, Brad, 1979 (Box-folder 27: 32)
  - Roberts, Henry L., 1960-1962 (Box-folder 27: 33)
  - Roberts, Paul Craig, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 27: 34)
  - Roberts, Walter Orr, 1973 (Box-folder 27: 35)
  - Robinson, Alwyn, 1968 (Box-folder 27: 36)
  - Robinson, Anthony, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 27: 37)